costumeideazone.com 2016-10-17

# Costume Idea Zone Privacy Policy

* * *

### PRIVACY STATEMENT FOR COSTUME IDEA ZONE

##### AmazingFX has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. This statement discloses our information-gathering and dissemination practices for the Costume Idea Zone Web site.

##### This site contains links to other Web sites. AmazingFX is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

##### We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice, you can visit [the Network Advertising Initiative Web site](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). You can opt-out of third-party advertising cookies by using the NAI opt-out tool at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)

#### CHILDREN'S GUIDELINES

##### The Costume Idea Zone Web site does NOT collect personally identifiable online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification.

##### The Costume Idea Zone Web site does NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent.

#### USER INFORMATION DISPLAYED ON THE WEB SITE

##### Users of the Costume Idea Zone Web site can submit costume ideas by going to the [Submissions Page](http://costumeideazone.com/CIZ/Submit.aspx). Submissions are added to the site at the discretion of AmazingFX, and will be edited as deemed necessary by the AmazingFX staff. Submissions that are listed on the site will include the first and/or last name of the submitter, if name(s) are provided by submitter. If a name is not provided, the idea will be posted without attribution. No email addresses or other personal information will be displayed. Users who do not wish to receive attribution for costume ideas should say so in their email message.

##### Users who have a currently listed costume suggestion, and wish to change or remove the attribution information, should send email to: [customerservice@costumeideazone.com](mailto:customerservice@costumeideazone.com).

#### CONTACTING THE WEB SITE

##### If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact the Webmaster at: [customerservice@costumeideazone.com](mailto:customerservice@costumeideazone.com).
